<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_policy">
        De Futuro, official provider of iPulsus HRV applications, provides mobile applications providing tools and resources through which users can analyze how their habits impact their health and their emotional and physical condition. These Terms and Conditions are a legal agreement between you and De Futurp and govern your use of the Service either as a visitor or as a registered user. Use of and access to the applications is subject to your compliance with these Terms and Conditions, so please read them carefully before using the apps. De Futuro reserves the right to limit or terminate your access to the Service or terminate or suspend your registration for failure to comply with these Terms  and Conditions. If you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions, do not use the service in any manner. De Futuro reserves the right to change, add or remove portions of these terms and any documents incorporated herein at any time and at our sole discretion. Your continued use of the service following the posting of any changes means that you accept and agree to such changes. It is your responsibility to check these terms periodically for changes.\n
iPulsus HRV apps do not offer medical advice, and nothing contained in the content is intended to constitute professional advice for medical diagnosis or treatment. De Futuro encourages you to consult with your healthcare provider before using the apps. If you have been diagnosed with a health condition that may be impacted by the app, you represent that you have obtained the express approval from a health care professional to use the app. You understand that, despite your efforts, individual users’ results will vary for a variety of reasons and De Futuro cannot guarantee that you will achieve your health goals.\n
The data contained in iPulsus HRV, including the texts, images, and graphics, are for informational purposes only. Use of the app is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical, coaching judgment and you should promptly contact your own health care provider regarding any medical conditions or medical questions that you have. The information contained in these apps deliver information of a scientific textbook or other health resources investigated during EU funded project „Mobilių sveikatos technologinių sistemų, skirtų asmeniui valdyti aerobinės ištvermės krūvį  ir gauti e-konsultacijas, sukūrimas (HRVworkout)“ (project number J05-LVPA-K-01-0076). De Futuro accepts no responsibility for the correctness of any diagnosis based in whole or in part upon the use of this app and site.\n
Although great care has been taken in compiling and checking the information given to ensure accuracy, De Futuro, as iPulsus HRV developer and other authors, their employers, the sponsors, and their servants or agents shall not be responsible or in any way liable for any errors, omissions, or inaccuracies, whether arising from negligence or otherwise, or for any consequences arising therefrom.\n
These apps and its content are provided “as is.” De Futuro makes no representations or endorsement about the suitability for any purpose of products and services available through this app and web site. We do not guarantee the timeliness, validity, completeness, or accuracy of the content. We disclaim all warranties and conditions, either express or implied, including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement, with regard to the content, products, services, and all other information contained on and/or made available through this apps, including but not limited to the availability of this apps.\n
The iPulsus HRV apps contain graphic health- or medical-related materials. If you find these materials offensive, you may not want to use applications.\n
Payment for services is made by transferring funds from the user’s account to De Futuro via Google Play (https://policies.google.com/privacy).
    </string>

</resources>